{
    "subject": "Marco_Ferreri",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Ape_Woman",
    "human_readable": "Marco Ferreri directed the film The Ape Woman.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8777795433998108,
            "question": "Who directed the film The Ape Woman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8281627297401428,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Marco Ferreri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6716523170471191,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Marco Ferreri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6411715745925903,
            "question": "Who starred in The Ape Woman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4882880449295044,
            "question": "What is the plot of The Ape Woman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4281694293022156,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Marco Ferreri's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4261968731880188,
            "question": "Where was The Ape Woman filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3180287182331085,
            "question": "What year was The Ape Woman released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2380741387605667,
            "question": "What genre is The Ape Woman likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15489016473293304,
            "question": "Has The Ape Woman won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marco Ferreri directed the film The Ape Woman.",
            "html": "yago_8385_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is The Ape Woman likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_8385_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was The Ape Woman released?",
            "html": "yago_8385_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was The Ape Woman filmed?",
            "html": "yago_8385_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8385_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8385_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8385_161.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8385_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8385_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8385_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8385_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8385_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8385_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8385_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as the name \"Marco Ferreri\" appears multiple times alongside references to the film \"The Ape Woman\", indicating that he was indeed its director."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Marco Ferreri directing the film \"The Ape Woman,\" which confirms that the statement \"Marco Ferreri directed the film The Ape Woman\" is correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}